Hello everyone, I am Shiori Nagata and Misato Honda of NOTE Call Me.
So today we will be recording with these two.
We will be looking at poetry. Please give us your best regards.
Surprisingly, this is the first time for me to do this.
It's my first time.
And for today's program, I would like to introduce these winter cosmetics we just bought.
We just went shopping at the Loft in Shibuya.
How much did we buy?
Surprisingly, we didn't go shopping for cosmetics together very often.
But we met a lot of people. At the cosmetics department.
Hugh many times.
Oh, I saw him.
I was so excited.
I got lost. It's a big place.
Kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk. We're still nervous.
One at a time, then.
Then let's introduce them right away.
Okay, let's start with the winner of the jakkemono.
Sachagu-jakkenpoi!
Then, I will introduce them first.
First of all, this way!
Paran!
ELJUTA Grace on Emulsion
It's a hair treatment.
Yes, I know, it's winter,
Hair gets dry and static electricity makes it snap! I bet you have dry hair and static electricity that causes it to snap!
I guess there are times when your hair gets dry and static electricity causes it to snap.
The deciding factor was that I've always wanted one.
So I picked it up.
Finally!
Yay, the first one!
Then I'll go with the hair-related one too.
This way! Loretta's glitter puffs!
This is the one that's been all over social networking sites.
Hair and makeup artists often use it, so I decided to buy it.
Oh, that's great!
It sparkles, doesn't it?
Oh, I'm glad. Everyone says it doesn't sparkle much.
Loretta, let's make it sparkle too.
They're all matching.
Yes, this is the second one.
Yes, this is the second one. It's not the first one.
It was the first one.
Next is Bonjune Moist Up Ready Skin Pack.
I chose the highly moisturizing type.
Yes, this is the one I put on my face before putting on makeup,
It's a little pack, kind of a square pack, like a cheek cheek or a nose pack,
I put it on my cheeks and nose like this, and then apply makeup,
If you put on makeup after applying this pack, your skin will not be dry at all.
It's great.
I carry it with me to live performances and work. I carry it with me to gigs and work.
Indeed. Me too then, skincare related,
Estline Deka 365 softening type.
This is lotion. I'm out of lotion right now, so I was looking for something moisturizing.
I was looking for something moisturizing, and I found it in a big, big, most conspicuous place.
I found it because it was around.
I'm going to moisturize with this.
Then, next, cosmetics?
Makeup? Well, here we go first!
Lilimu's Sharpness Brush! Wow! I've been wanting one of these for a long time.
Yes, I like to draw a line under my eyes and on my lower lids to make my eyes look bigger.
I lent it to you because I thought it would be easy to draw! I lent it to you because I thought it would make my eyes look many times bigger!
I received the brush! Thank you so much!
I bought my brush...
Here! This is Picasso eyeshadow brush!
It looks so cute in the package.
I've been curious about it every time I go to the store, so I finally bought it!
I've been into putting color on the corner of my eyes recently.
I want to use this to put a little bit of color on the corner of my eyes.
I'd like to apply it beautifully. Next is this one.
I bought it too. They are matching. Chi-chan told me about it, and I bought one too.
Tweezer is for false eyelashes, and Sucre Momochan uses it.
Sucre Momochan uses it to make her eyelashes into bunches.
She always used this to make her eyelashes grow so tightly that I could remember them, so I thought I'd use it too.
I'm looking forward to it again. I'm looking forward to the day I can pinch my eyelashes.
Here's another matching product. Seino!This is another matching product. Se-no!
Ta-da!
This is Canmake's Creamy Touch Liner No. 11.
Yes! Same color.
Yes, it's the same color.
It's a really nice color, and I'm still using it,
Yes, it's kind of a grayish color.
Yes, it is.
Not too dark.
Brownish.
It's a brownish color. Cloudy gray.
Gray. Something just right, isn't it?
Yes, it is. It's good.
It doesn't make your eyes look too bright.
It's just a little bit warm and fuzzy, just the way we like it.
Yeah.
Next, I'll introduce the blush.
It's Lilimu's Veil Glow blush in No. 01 Orange Mist.
I've been wearing orange and coral makeup lately,
I've been using only pink blush, so I wanted to buy an orange blush,
I was thinking of buying an orange blush, and I saw that you had it.
Thank you very much. It definitely looks good on me. I'm so happy. The color is so cute, I'm looking forward to the day I can wear it.
And I'm also looking forward to the day when I can wear this,
There were so many shimmering colors that I couldn't even count how many colors there were, and the colors blended well with my skin,
I thought it would be cute if they had sparkles in their eyes. I thought it would be cute with sparkling eyes. I thought, "Let's make my tear ducts illuminated, too. So I got this one.
Yay! I'm going to buy another one, Relimuial. Here it is.Yay!!! I buy one more relimuar. This one.
It's the Multi-Hit Liner in #01 Gegur Beige. I've been into over lips lately,
I was hoping to get a lip liner,
When I got out there, Ms. Hashihara offered me a lip liner.
I had to buy it and finally did.
I would like to use this.
I'll introduce two at once.
It's a Sipisipi point concealer in a color called Strawberry Milk.
The name is cute, but it's pinkish when it comes to making tear troughs and such.
It makes my tear ducts look puffy all at once, so I'm looking forward to it.
The name is cute, and it's pink.
Pink concealers are rare, aren't they?
This is Nail Eyelash Mute Brown.
It says it's a color that's neither black nor brown, and it's a mascara,
If I had a day where I wanted to be gentle with my lashes,
I thought it would be cute if I applied just the right in-between color,
So I got the color I tried for the first time.
Here's the last one.
Brown Glam, an eye tutorial eye palette.
Gel Chima Peach Chorus.
This is so cute.
Like a calculator, yeah, very cute.
Hey, I was looking at it thinking it's cute, and Omiru-chan, too.
That's right. Different color pink.
I have No. 02.
I have the number 02. I have number 02.
It's on the package, you know, because it has a number on it,
Oh, it was easy to remember the numbers 1, 2, and 3.
I'm looking forward to it.
I didn't have many eye palettes like this.
Oh, I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm glad.
I'm the last one too.
And I have an eyeshadow, too,
Let's see, Clio Pro Eye Palette #01.
Simply pink.
Yes, I've always loved pink eyeshadows,
But there's one color in pink that I like to put on my eyes.
Cute.
This one has so many of my favorite colors in it,
Simply pink.
It's like a mix of brown and pink.
There's a lot of glitter in it.
Oh, it also comes with a brush.
Yes, I really appreciate that it comes with a brush.
When you're working, it's really nice to have a brush, isn't it?
You can take just one of these with you.
That's how I feel about it.
I am looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
Eh, let me know the day you're wearing the pretty.
I'll let you know. Please tell me too, Chi-chan.
Thank you. I'll let you know.
So, today I tried to introduce winter cosmetics.
How did you like it? What did you think?
I was kind of nervous. Is it right? I wondered if I was doing it right.
It's such a pleasure to see cosmetics lined up in front of you like this.
I am very happy.
What do you care most about in your face?
Well, I don't know. Lately, I've been obsessed with my tear troughs.
That's why I want to be able to use them well.
That's nice. I also spend a lot of time on my eyes,
I put on a light pink concealer, like this tear trough concealer I just bought,
I'm really into drawing shadows on the tear troughs with pink eyeshadow after applying a light pink concealer, like this tear trough concealer I just bought.
You draw them in pink? That's nice.
Then the pink blends in with the pink on top of the eyes and makes the eyes look bigger at once,
I recommend it.
I guess it's like that.
Yes, we have recommended products, so please try them.
That's all for now.
Bye bye.